Hello everyone, this is Morisaki Win for Enjoy Simple English
今年度からナビゲーターを務める森崎ウィンです
毎週月曜日はオリジナルのショートストーリーをお伝えします
今日はロックバンド、バンド結成
親友のミノルにバンドを結成しないかと持ちかけるコージーですが
ギターをどちらが担当するかで揉めてしまい話がまとまりません
さてどんな結末になるのでしょうか
Here's today's story
ミノル、おはよう。
コウジ、おはよう。
昨夜、ミュージックTVのプログラムを見たことがありましたか?
もちろん、世界に見つかることはありませんでした。
勝者は最もクールなバンドだと思っていました。
私たちはそれをやるべきだと思っています。
やるべきなの?
バンドを始めましょう!
それはできません。
私たちの学校はバンドクラブがありません。
あるいはフォークソングクラブもあります。
ブラスバンドは、私たちの学校で唯一のミュージッククラブです。
私は学校でクラブの活動を話していません。
では、何を話しているのですか?
私の父の友人はミュージックスタジオを持っています。
昨日、彼は私たちの家に来て、私たちのミュージックスタジオを自由に使うことを言っていたのです。
彼は、私たちも彼のミュージックスタジオを使うことを言っていたのです。
本当ですか?
Wow! That's great!
Yeah! So we don't have to spend time or effort trying to start a club at school.
And it won't cost us anything!
All we have to do is form a band and we're all set!
That's amazing, Koji! Who else will be in our band?
I don't know yet. I was so excited that I wanted to talk about it with you first.
Got it. So...
Who are we looking for?
Well, we need someone to play the bass, drums, and keyboards.
I can play the guitar.
Huh? I'm the guitarist.
No, no, no. You came to me because you knew I could play the guitar, right?
No. I came to you because we've been friends since elementary school.
I didn't know you play the guitar.
How good are you?
Pretty good.
Are you better than me?
Just listen to me play.
Okay, then you can do the bass.
Huh? Why?
If you can play the guitar, I know you can play the bass.
It's the same type of instrument, right?
That's not fair.
Why do I have to play the bass?
You can play the guitar too, so you do it.
I will only play the guitar, and I'm the leader of the band, so I make the decisions.
What did you just say? You are the leader.
Of course. I was the one to suggest starting a band.
I'm the leader, and I'm playing the guitar. Got it?
No, I don't get it.
What's the problem?
Well...
リーダーは全てのバンドをリーダーにならないといけないのです。
あなたは自分自身が自分自身だと言っているのです。
まあ、私がそれをできるかどうかは分からないのですが。
分かりました。
私はあなたを長い間知っています。
あなたは良いリーダーではありません。
うーん。
それで終わりです!
バンドは終わりました!
コウジ、バンドは始まる前に終わることはできないのですか?
Oh yeah!
もうね、みのる君とこうじ君に言ってあげたい
ベースが一番モテるんだぞ!と
まあ僕ベース弾いてませんが
はは、はい!
バンドを結成するフォーマバンド
もうこれ僕も知らなかったですね、こんな言い方があるとは
ということでぜひ皆さん、あのバンド始めるなら
ベースをまず取りに行ってください
さてホームページのNHK語学
スマートフォン用のNHK語学アプリではですね
1週間前の放送ストリーミングで聞くことができます
繰り返し繰り返しぜひぜひたくさん聞いてください
やっぱ耳慣れしていくってのは大事ですよね
はいそれではSee you tomorrow